Sakura-chan.
さくらちゃん
yes.
はい
Could you come over here for a moment?
ちょっとこっち来てくれる?
Sit down.
座って
Can you play around with this again?
これまたいじってくれる?
from the beginning
最初手から
...
Look at the destination
先 っぽいじってみ
Ru?
る?
It's getting a little bigger.
ちょっと 大きくなってきたね
Want to add it at any time you like?
好きなタイミングで加えてみる?
Are you going to lick it already?
もう舐めちゃう?
Shall I lick it?
舐めちゃう?
good
いい
Yo.
よ
That's amazing.
すごい やつが
copper?
どう?
That big dick.
そのでっかいチンチン
delicious?
おいしい?
delicious.
おいしい
Because it comes up from below.
下から上がるから
Should I make it more slimy?
もっとヌルヌルにしちゃう?
Turn to me while sucking.
しゃぶりながらこっち向いて
Don't let go.
離しちゃダメ
Don't let it come out of your mouth.
口から出しちゃダメ
Being eaten all the time.
ずっと食われてて
Yeah.
うん
Move your tongue around inside it.
その中で舌いっぱい動かして
Lick it as much as you like.
い っぱい舐めて
Use your hands too.
手も使って
Squeeze just the tip with your hand.
手で先っぽいだけしこしこして
Hard dick.
硬いチンチン
Kuro-chan, stand up.
黒ちゃん立って
I took the skirt Dorigon.
スカートドリゴン取った
I'll put it in myself.
自分でチンチン入れちゃう
Manjul is making a lot of noise.
マンジュルでチンチンテカテカしてる
What do you think, Kuro-chan?
どう、黒ちゃん?
Manfish?
マンコウ?
You have to make it the biggest one, Kuro-chan.
一番大きくしなきゃダメだよ、黒ちゃん
Because that's how it works.
そうやって動いてるから
Make my cock harder
チ ンチンもっと硬くして
Ru.
る
Manjul has a great penis.
マ ンジュルですんごいチンチンです
Deep above the feet.
足上の奥
Open everything.
全部開くんだよ
Please open your pussy.
おまんくん開いてください
Can I break it into you?
ぶち込んでいい?
It's cramped, isn't it, this mancow?
狭いでしょ、このマンコウ
Kuro-chan, you moved quickly and saved him.
黒ちゃん、一回早く動いて生かしたね
I'll take it as hard as I can.
思いっきり取りにしてもらう
Kuro-chan, can I give you a lot?
黒ちゃん、いっぱい出していい?
Sakura-chan, I'll cover your face.
さくらちゃん、顔かけるからね
It's all over my face.
めっちゃ顔中についてるよ
It's still that way.
そのまんまだ
Let me talk again.
また 喋らせて
It was done neatly and neatly.
ちゃんと綺麗にできた
Kuro-chan, open your pussy.
黒ちゃん、マンコウ開いて
Just say bye-bye and see.
このままバイバイして、じゃあほら